Guide to the CONSOL Energy, Inc. Mine Maps and Records, 1857-2010 AIS.1991.16
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Survey Books, 1880s-1990s; XVI.
  - Outside Notes, 7.
    - Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 738; Property surveys; Lick Run Mine, First Pool Mine, Montour Mine # 8; Baltimore & Ohio Railroad; Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 744; West Newton Mine, Ocean Mine # 5; Property surveys, Lines and levels (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 744; Property lines and levels, Contours and elevations; Forest Hill Mine, Ocean Mine # 5; Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 766; Drill hole locations, Property surface surveys; Banning Mine # 1, Euclid Mine, Helen Mine, Waverly Mine (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 766; Drill hole locations, Property surface surveys; Banning Mine # 1, Euclid Mine, Helen Mine, Waverly Mine; Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 797; Property surveys, Farm and pit locations; Hodgen Mine, Steiner Vein Mine (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 797; Property surveys, Farm and pit locations; Hodgen Mine, Steiner Vein Mine; Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 825; Property surveys, Shaft measurements, Land connections; Equitable Mine, Ocean Mine # 5, Guiler Mine, Shaner Mine (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 922; Banning Mine, Ocean Mine, Warden Mine, Somers Mine (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 925; Euclid Mine, Banning Mine # 1, Ocean Mine, Warden Mine (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 947; Risher Mine, Eureka Mine, Warden Mine, Ocean Mine, Banning Mine (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 953; Ocean Mine, Cincinnati Mine, Banning Mine, Bunola Mine (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 975; Banning Mine # 1, Ocean Mine, Walton Mine, Euclid Mine; Pittsburgh & West Virginia Railroad (Box 130, Folder 18)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 992; Banning Mine # 1, 2, Euclid Mine, Warden Mine, Eureka Mine, Waverly Mine; Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad (Box 130, Folder 19)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 1329; Property Locations; Baltimore & Ohio Railroad; West Newton Mine, Ocean Mine; Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 1370; Property surveys and levels, Building locations, Road locations; Forest Hill Mine, Ocean Mine # 2 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 1442; Property surveys and levels; Yough Slope Mine, Ocean Mine # 2, Lovedale Mine, Forest Hill Mine; Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 1497; Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad; Building locations, Power line locations, Road locations, Property survey (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 4002; Warden Mine, Ocean Mine # 2, Banning Mine # 2; Road locations (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 4008; Port Royal Mine, Bigley Mine, Banning Mine # 1, 2 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 4014; Ocean Mine, Euclid Mine (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 4023; Banning Mine # 2, Apollo Mine, Ocean Mine; Road locations, Railroads (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 4036; West Newton Mine, Ocean Mine # 2, Warden Mine, Lovedale Mine, Elizabeth Mine; Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 4044; Banning Mine # 2, Apollo Mine, Wick Haven Mine; Property surveys (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 8, book no. 4056; Wick Haven Mine, Banning Mine # 1, Ocean Mine # 2, Yough Mine # 2; Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 165; Store lots; Whitsett Mine, Banning Mine, Euclid Mine (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 279; Land tract survey, Road survey; Baltimore & Ohio Railroad; Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 280; Land tract connections; Eureka Mine topography (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 331; Duplicate of book 150; Property lines; Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 350; Tracks at Waverly Mine; Contours and property levels (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 351; Topographical survey; Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 415; Motor roads; Banning Mine # 1, Darr Mine, Waverly Mine, Euclid Mine, Youghiogheny & Ohio Mine # 2 (Box 131, Folder 11)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 516; Banning Mine # 2, Port Royal Mine, Waverly Mine; Baltimore & Ohio Railroad topography; Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 601; Baltimore & Ohio Railroad; Eureka Mine (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 601; Banning Mine, Eureka Mine; Multiple tracts of land; Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 602; Banning Mine # 1, Eureka Mine, Wick Haven Mine (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 629; Public road survey, Deed information, Railroad locations, Land property surveys; Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 655; Property and farm surveys; Banning Mine # 2, Darr Mine; Contour lines; Whitsett Mine levels (Box 131, Folder 14)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 658; Property lines and levels; Banning Mine # 1, 2, Wick Haven Mine, Waverly Mine; Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 672; Waverly Mine levels; Property surveys; Cedar Creek; Houses at Banning Mine # 3 (Box 131, Folder 15)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 680; Banning Mine # 3 waterline, Eureka Mine # 1, 4; Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad, Baltimore & Ohio Railroad; Property surveys, Building locations; Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 681; Eureka Mine, Euclid Mine; Property levels (Box 131, Folder 16)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 708; Banning Mine # 2, Eureka Mine, Waverly Mine; Property lines and levels, Pit locations (Box 131, Folder 17)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 736; Property lines and levels; Waverly Mine, Eureka Mine, Banning Mine # 2; Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad (Box 131, Folder 18)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 748; Property surveys; Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad; Houses on properties; Outside notes, Division No. 9, book no. 834; Banning Mine, Euclid Mine, Black Diamond Mine, Eureka Mine, Arnold Mine; Road locations, Property surveys, Water well locations (Box 131, Folder 19)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 10, book no. 510; Fairhaven Mine, First Pool Mine; Outside notes, Division No. 10, book no. 518; Property line locations; Fairhaven Mine, First Pool Mine, Lick Run Mine, Baltimore & Ohio Railroad (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 10, book no. 526; Property line locations; Fairhaven Mine; Outside notes, Division No. 10, book no. 526; Baltimore & Ohio Railroad survey; First Pool Mine, Fairhaven Mine; Land levels (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 11, book no. 604; Bertha Mine, C Mine; Shannon-Montour Mine; Outside notes, Division No. 11, book no. 642; Property lines and topography (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 11, book no. 771; Farmland surveys; Chartiers Southern Railroad; Gas well locations; Coal Bluff Mine surface (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 11, book no. 785; Pittsburgh Coal Meridian; Gas lines; Coal Bluff Mine survey (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 11, book no. 796; Lovedale Mine, Roseburg Mine, Walton Mine, Yough Mine # 1; Property survey, Lines and levels, Pit and creek locations (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 11, book no. 799; Aliquippa Mine surface, Pine Run Mine, Camden Mine, Coal Valley Mine; Property lines and levels, Building locations (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 11, book no. 1273; Property surveys, Railroad notes; Outside notes, Division No. 12, book no. 760; Property levels and connections, Farm lines, Surface levels; Equitable Mine, Mongah Mine (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 12, book no. 760; Property levels and connections, Farm lines, Surface levels; Equitable Mine, Mongah Mine; Outside notes, Division No. 12, book no. 772; Property lines and levels; Ella Mine, Sunnyside Mine, Gallatin Mine, Roy Leper's Mine, Wilson's Mine (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 12, book no. 772; Property lines and levels; Ella Mine, Sunnyside Mine, Gallatin Mine, Roy Leper's Mine, Wilson's Mine; Outside notes, Division No. 12, book no. 817; Sunnyside Mine, McClure Tract, Mongah Mine, Gallatin Mine, Manown Mine (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 12, book no. 817; Sunnyside Mine, McClure Tract, Mongah Mine, Gallatin Mine, Manown Mine; Outside notes, Division No. 12, book no. 993; Gas well locations, House and street locations, Bore hole locations; Bridgeville Mine, Oak Mine, Saw Mill Run Mine, South Hills Mine (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 12, book no. 993; Gas well locations, House and street locations, Bore hole locations; Bridgeville Mine, Oak Mine, Saw Mill Run Mine, South Hills Mine; Outside notes, Division No. 12, book No. 1437; Road locations, Levels, Gas line locations Equitable Mine, Mongah Mine (Box 132, Folder 12)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 12, book no. 4050; Montour Mine # 8, Delmont Mine, Black Diamond Mine; Property surveys; Outside notes, Division No. 13, book no. 676; Apollo Mine, Sunnyside Mine, Tremont Mine, Gallatin Mine, Fayette City Mine; Property lines, Side track, Levels (Box 132, Folder 13)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 13, book no. 707; Gallatin Mine levels; Property lines and levels, Gas line locations; Kathryn Alberti Mine, John Allen Mine, Connelly Mine, Apollo Mine surface (Box 132, Folder 14)
    - Outside notes, Division No. 13, 746; Tremont Mine, Manown Mine, Gallatin Mine; Property lines and levels (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - Property Surveys, 8.
    This subseries includes books that focus on property surveys around or of the mines. Farmlands, estates and other land tracts are detailed and drawn out with levels and elevations.
    - Property Surveys book no. 1; Williams Property; Property Levels book no. 2 (Box 132, Folder 16)
    - Property Surveys book no. 3; Property Notes book no. 4 (Box 132, Folder 17)
    - Property Surveys book no. 6; Osborn Saegar and Co.; William Gressley Farm; Property book no. 7; Greene County (Box 132, Folder 18)
    - Property Surveys book no. 7; Hagerty Farm; Property Surveys book no. 14; Osborne Saegar and Co. at Jacob's Creek, Westmoreland County (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Property Surveys book no. 30, outside; Greene County; Property Surveys book no. 30, Osborne Saegar and Co., Youghiogheny River, East side (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Property Surveys book no. 36; Frashier, Shearer, Gween, Fleming; Property Surveys book no. 50; Smock surface (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Property Surveys book no. 58; Rostraver Township, Westmoreland County; Property Surveys book no. 67, Chartiers Township (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Property Surveys book no. 138, Redstone Property; Property Surveys book no. 164, Scott Heirs, Steiner Custom Pit (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Property Surveys book no. 186, Peters Township, Washington County; Property Surveys book no. 194, Douglass Hollow (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Property Surveys book no. 197; Outside notes, Division No. 1; Farm surveys; Property Surveys book no. 199, T. B. Hixon Farm, William Sheets Estate, Innes and Reynolds, Jason Spears Estate, John Galley (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Property Surveys book no. 284, D. E. Parke, Thompsonville lots; Property Surveys book no. 487, North of Fayette City adjoining Monongahela River; Consolidation Coal & Coke Co. (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Property Surveys book no. 514; Survey to connect mines of True Meridian; Property Surveys book no. 514; True Meridian Surveys (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Property Surveys book no. 530; Land tract survey; Property Surveys book no. 533; Outside notes, Division No. 6; Topographical line levels (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Property Surveys book no. 628; O.I.C. Mine property, Moon Run topography, Essen Mine; # 2 property, Partridge Road location; Property Surveys book no. 636; Monthly estimates (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Property Surveys book no. 639; F. L. Robbins tract, J. Murry Clark Farms; Property Surveys book no. 671; Lime Island surveys (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - Property Surveys book no. 671; Lime Island notes, Sandwich Fueling Dock notes; Property Surveys book no. 749; Levels and lines, Topography (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - Property Surveys book no. 769; Farmland survey, Land connection survey; Property Surveys book no. 775; Farmland surveys and connections (Box 133, Folder 14)
    - Property Surveys book no. 780; Outside notes (Box 133, Folder 15)
    - Property Surveys book no. 781; Farmland surveys and connections; Property Surveys book no. 786 (Box 133, Folder 16)
    - Property Surveys book no. 786; Outside notes; Property Surveys book no. 801; Outside notes, Lines and levels (Box 133, Folder 17)
    - Property Surveys book no. 801; Outside notes, Lines and levels; Property Surveys book no. 824; Outside notes, Division No. 11; Farmland survey, Levels and elevations (Box 133, Folder 18)
    - Property Surveys book no. 824; Outside notes, Division No. 11; Farmland survey, Lines and levels; Property Surveys book no. 857; Outside notes, Hill heights and measurements (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Property Surveys book no. 858; Outside notes, Hill and line measurements; Property Surveys book no. 923; Contour levels; Moore Farm (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Property Surveys book no. 973; Property Surveys book no. 974; Outside notes, Division No. 12 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Property Surveys book no. 974; Outside notes, Division No. 12; Property Surveys book no. 977; Outside notes, Division No. 5 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Property Surveys book no. 978; Outside notes, Division No. 2 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Property Surveys book no. 981; Property Surveys book no. 983; Outside notes, Division No. 5 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Property Surveys book no. 985; Outside notes, Division No. 2 (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Property Surveys book no. 986; Outside notes, Division No. 5; Contour levels (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - Property Surveys book no. 989; Outside notes, Division No. 2; Dickson Mine, Lindley Mine (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - Property Surveys book no. 1011; Oil well locations; Creedmoor Mine; Property Surveys book no. 1027 (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Property Surveys book no. 1066; Outside notes, Division No. 8; Property Surveys book no. 1084; Road locations (Box 134, Folder 11)
    - Property Surveys book no. 1097; Outside notes, Division No. 8; Property Surveys book no. 1145; Lime Island surveys and soundings (Box 134, Folder 12)
    - Property Surveys book no. 1152; Outside notes, Division No. 11; Martin Coulson Farm; Property Surveys book no. 1325 (Box 134, Folder 13)
    - Property Surveys book no. 1364; Surveys of Mines not owned by Pittsburgh Coal Co.; Property Surveys book no. 1754; Elevations (Box 134, Folder 14)
    - Property Surveys book no. 4000; Little Beaver Creek, miscellaneous notes (Box 134, Folder 15)
    - Property Surveys book no. 4001; Little Beaver Creek, miscellaneous notes (Box 134, Folder 16)
    - Property Surveys book no. 4004; Little Beaver Creek, miscellaneous notes (Box 134, Folder 17)
    - Property Surveys book no. 4045; Little Beaver Creek, miscellaneous notes (Box 134, Folder 18)
    - Property Surveys; Ellsworth surveys; Property Surveys; Levels (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Property Surveys; Logan's Ferry (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Property Surveys; Millars Run; Property surveys, Mine surveys, Measurements (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Property Surveys; Multiple mine surveys; Property Surveys; Elevations (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Property Surveys; Farm lines, Measurements; Property Surveys (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Topography, 9.
    The books in this subseries illustrate the topography of the mines and other land that was of interest to CONSOL.
    - Topography book no. 131; Outside lines west side, Youghiogheny River; Levels; Topography book no. 144; Plum Run for Railroad (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Topography book no. 145, Plum Run; Topography book no. 147; Whitsett heirs' property; Banning Mine # 2; Building surveys (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Topography book no. 184, Levels on line staked out on Plum Run and Little Chartiers Creek; Topography book no. 185, Line on Chartiers Run from Huston (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Topography book no. 251, Division No. 9, Darr Mine, Banning Mine, Whitsett Mine, Waverly Mine; Topography book no. 268, Surface, Division No. 9, Wick Haven Mine, Banning Mine, Eureka Mine to Banning Mine, Baltimore & Ohio Railroad (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Topography book no. 272, Redstone Creek; Topography book no. 273, Redstone Creek; South side contour book (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - Topography book no. 274, Redstone Creek, North side Contour Book; Topography book no. 275, Redstone Creek (Box 135, Folder 11)
    - Topography book no. 276, Redstone Creek; Topography book no. 390, Whitsett Mine property lines (Box 135, Folder 12)
    - Topography book no. 502, Redstone Creek; Topography book no. 519, Redstone Creek (Box 135, Folder 13)
    - Topography book no. 520, Redstone Creek; Topography book no. 521, Outside notes, Division No. 9, Whitsett Mine (Box 135, Folder 14)
    - Topography book no. 522, Redstone Creek; Topography book no. 523, Redstone Creek, Levels (Box 135, Folder 15)
    - Topography book no. 530; Topography book no. 533; Redstone Creek (Box 135, Folder 16)
    - Topography book no. 536; Topography book no. 538 (Box 135, Folder 17)
    - Topography book no. 538; Topography book no. 548, Property lines (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Topography book no. 558, Preliminary line from Hill to Greer; Topography book no. 580, Land purchased (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Topography book no. 668; Wilson property, McKee property, Morrison property; Topography book no. 960, Outside notes, Division No. 12; Property surveys, Lines and levels (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Topography book no. 960; Outside notes, Division No. 12; Property surveys, Lines and levels, Topography; Swisshelm Hollow; Private work (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Topography (Box 136, Folder 5)
- Traverse Logs, 1880s-1990s; XVII.
  Traverse logs were used by surveyors and mine engineers to calculate and convert the field survey data collected in the Survey Books to latitude (north-south) and departure (east-west). The calculated information was then in a form such that the data could be added to the surface and underground maps and drawings maintained by the mining company. These books are arranged in alphabetical order by mine name.
  - Albany Mine (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Albany Mine-Chamouni Mine-Snowhill Mine-Anchov Mine (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Moved to AIS.2004.22, Box 12, Folder 1 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Moved to AIS.2004.22, Box 12, Folder 2 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Moved to AIS.2004.22, Box 13, Folder 1-4 (Box 139, Folder 1-4)
  - Alice Mine and Washington Mine (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Alice Mine (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Aliquippa Mine and Camden Mine (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Aliquippa Mine Inside (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Allison Mine (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Apollo Mine and Fayette City Mine (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Apollo Mine (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Arnold Mine Inside (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Arnold Mine Outside (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Banner Mine Inside (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Banning Mine # 2 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Black Diamond Mine Inside (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Boon Mine (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Briar Hill Mine (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Bridgeville Mine (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Bunola Mine Inside (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Camden Mine Inside (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Catsburg Mine and Black Diamond Mine, Vol. 1 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Catsburg Mine and Black Diamond Mine, Vol. 2 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Chamouni Mine Inside (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Champion Mine (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Champion Mine Inside and Outside (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Champion Mine Outside (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Cherry Mine (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Cherry Valley Mine (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Cincinnati Mine Inside (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Cincinnati Mine Outside (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Coal Bluff Mine Inside (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Creedmoor Mine (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Coal Bluff Mine (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - Crescent Mine Inside, Vol. 2 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Crescent Mine Inside, Vol. 3 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Crescent Mine and Vigilant Mine Inside, Vol. 1 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Crescent Mine and Vigilant Mine Outside (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Crescent Mine # 2 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Delmont Mine (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Dickson Mine (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Eclipse Mine Inside, Vol. 1 (Now Crescent Mine # 2) (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Eclipse Mine Inside, Vol. 2 (Now Crescent Mine # 2) (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Elizabeth Mine (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Emery Field (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Equitable Mine Inside (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Essen Mine # 1 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Essen Mine # 3 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Essen Mine # 2 - # 3 Inside, Vol. 1 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Essen Mine # 2 - # 3 Inside, Vol. 2 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Eureka Mine Inside (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Fair Haven Mine (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Fair Haven Mine surface (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Fayette City Mine (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Federal Mine # 2 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Ferry-Risher Mine Inside (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Ferry-Risher Mine Outside (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - First Pool Mine, 376-A-6 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - First Pool Mine - Montour # 8 Inside, Vol. 1 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - First Pool Mine - Montour # 8 Inside, Vol. 2 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - First Pool Mine # 1 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - First Pool Mine # 2 surface (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Gallatin Mine Inside (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Gospel Mine (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Gospel Mine (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Grant Mine (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Guffy Coal Field surface (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Hanna Mine and Braznell Mine (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Harmar Mine # 1 Inside (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Harrison Mine (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Henderson Mine (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Henry W. Oliver Mine (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Hostetter Mine (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Hutchinson Mine (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Imperial Mine Stripping (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Lake Superior Mine (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Jamison Mine Dept. Records up to 1949 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Laurel Hill Mine # 1 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Laurel Hill Mine # 2 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Laurel Hill Mine # 5 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Lick Run Mine Inside (now Montour Mine # 10) (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Lick Run Mine Inside (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Little Beaver Mine (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Little Redstone Mine Inside (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Little Squaw Mine (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Lovedale Mine (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Lovedale Mine Inside (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Montour Mine # 10, Vol. 1 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Montour Mine # 10, Vol. 2 (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Montour Mine # 10, Vol. 3 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Montour Mine # 10, Vol. 4 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Montour Mine # 10, Vol. 5 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Montour Junction (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Montour Mine # 9, Vol. 1 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - Montour Mine # 9, Vol. 2 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Montour Railroad (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Manown Mine (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Manown Mine Outside (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Mansfield Mine (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Maple Creek Mine (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Margerum Mine (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Meadowlands Mine (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Midland Mine # 2 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Midland Mine Inside, Vol. 3 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Midland Mine # 1 Inside, Vol. 1 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - Midland Mine # 3 Inside (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - Mongah Mine Inside (Box 163, Folder 1)